adstation.com 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy - AdStation by Adknowledge

_Effective December 30, 2013._

This Policy may change from time to time. Please check back frequently for updates.  
For additional information, please visit the [Adknowledge Privacy Center](http://www.adknowledge.com/privacy/ "Adknowledge Privacy Center").

Adknowledge, Inc. and its list management line of business operations (“Adknowledge”, “we”, or “us”) respect and protect the privacy of consumers. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes what information we collect, how we use that information, and some of your privacy rights regarding that information.

**Collection of Information and Your Privacy Rights**

_What information we collect and how we collect it._

1.1. User Information. Adknowledge collects information from you when you voluntarily provide it to Adknowledge or one of its partners, through websites (owned and operated by Adknowledge or a third party) ; social networking, mobile, gaming and other applications providers; and other means (together, these sources are referenced hereafter as “Publishers”), or by others means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a “User Form”). In a User Form, Adknowledge or a third party may offer you incentives in exchange for providing information about yourself such as name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, and personal and online interests (together, “User Information”). Completing the User Form is voluntary and you are under no obligation to provide User Information.

1.2 Vendor List Information. Adknowledge may obtain information about you after you provide information to a third party and you permit that party (the “Seller”) to share the information, which Adknowledge subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise lawfully acquires. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education, marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and other information which you provided to the Seller (together, “Vendor List Information”). When acquiring Vendor List Information, Adknowledge requires assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Vendor List Information to Adknowledge and that the Adknowledge may lawfully use the Vendor List Information to transmit offers from advertisers.

1.3 User Behaviors Collected with Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Information. Adknowledge uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you, such as your Internet Protocol address and what Web browser you are using, with certain of your online behaviors, such as opening or clicking on a particular online advertisement. Additionally, Adknowledge may use other new and evolving sources of information and information gathering in the future (together, “Technology Information”).

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows Adknowledge and/or its partners to identify your IP address with corresponding information in Adknowledge’s database. Adknowledge and/or its partners may use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements, and use this information to help predict what other advertisements may be of interest to consumers and enable the receipt of customized advertisements or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, such as your email address, that we may share with any third party, solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To learn about how you can opt-out of the receipt of cookies, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. To learn about how you can remove cookies placed on your computer or prevent the placement of cookies on your computer, please see Section 4 below. To learn more about cookies in general, please visit [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

(b) Web beacons. A web beacon is programming code used to display an image on a web page and can also transfer an individual’s user identification to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about the individual. Web beacons enable Adknowledge to track certain Web sites you visit or advertisements you view online. Web beacons help determine products or services in which you may be interested and help track online behaviors for marketing purposes. More information about web beacons is available at <http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html>.

(c) Where Technology Information is Collected. Technology Information is collected directly from Adknowledge advertisements or indirectly through Publishers that Adknowledge contracts with to display advertisements. Such advertisements will usually be displayed within one of the following advertising vehicles:

_Websites_. Adknowledge may set a cookie on your computer when you view advertisements delivered on Publisher websites. After a cookie is set, Adknowledge may track how you interact with the advertisement and the Publisher website (for example, registering, purchasing, browsing, etc.).

_Software Programs_. Similar to Websites, Adknowledge displays banner advertisements in software programs that you may use.

_Email Databases_. Adknowledge and/or its partners may track your interaction with email advertisements sent to you (for example, by setting a cookie on your computer) on behalf of Publishers, advertisers or partner websites (for example, when you register, purchase, or browse in response to such email).

1.4 Outside Information. Adknowledge may lawfully receive information about you from third parties, such as information located in public databases (“Outside Information”).

1.5 No Information Collected from Minors. MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 18 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO ADKNOWLEDGE. If Adknowledge is notified it has personal information about a minor under the age of 18, that information will be promptly deleted from our database.

1.6 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means User Information, Vendor List Information, Technology Information, Outside Information, and any other information Adknowledge lawfully obtains about you.

**Use of Information and User Data**

_How we use and share the information we collect._

2.1 Discretion to Use Information. Information voluntarily provided to Adknowledge or lawfully obtained by Adknowledge is the property of Adknowledge and may be used by Adknowledge for any lawful purpose, including the sale, lease or transfer of the information to Publishers, advertisers and data aggregators, for marketing purposes. If you wish to end your email subscription with us or one of our Publishers, you may follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe or follow the instructions detailed at Section 4 below.

2.2 Targeted Advertising and Information. Adknowledge uses Individual Information to target advertising and other information, such as business, weather, entertainment, sports and general news alerts and similar information, more effectively. When an individual is online, Adknowledge uses Technology Information to associate an individual with their Individual Information and Adknowledge attempts to show information and advertising for products and services to which the person may respond. Adknowledge may use data collected from a response to one type of advertising or information for targeting advertisements or other information through a different venue. For example, Adknowledge may notice that you responded to a baseball banner advertisement and use that response to deliver a baseball-related advertisement and other information to you.

2.3 Legal Process. Adknowledge may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required by law.

2.4 Summary Data. Adknowledge may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

2.5 Business Transition. Adknowledge may transfer all or part of your Individual Information as part of a business transition such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale.

_How we store and protect the information we receive_.

2.6 Storage of Individual Information. Adknowledge stores Individual Information in a database on Adknowledge computers; the information is maintained and stored in encrypted form. In addition, Adknowledge’s computers have security measures, such as a firewall, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Adknowledge’s control. Adknowledge also maintains physical and procedural safeguards to protect Individual Information. Notwithstanding such measures, Adknowledge cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent these computers from being illegally accessed and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

**Privacy Practices of Third Parties**.

_Third Party privacy policies and use of cookies_.

3.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Publishers who place advertisements on the Internet may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about you. Adknowledge does not control Publishers’ use of such technology. Adknowledge may place cookies of its Publishers or advertisers who are under contract with Adknowledge, on your computer. These cookies may be placed at the time you open and/or click within email sent by Adknowledge or a Publisher under contract with Adknowledge. This Policy does not apply to the practices of Publishers or other companies that Adknowledge does not own or control or to people that Adknowledge does not employ or manage.

3.2 Links. The Publishers’ Website and email messages transmitted by Adknowledge on its own behalf or on behalf of Publishers may contain hypertext links to the Websites of third parties. Adknowledge is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

3.3 Affiliated Companies that are not Publishers. Adknowledge may disclose or transfer Individual Information to wholly owned or controlled Adknowledge entities in Adknowledge’s discretion.

**How You May Exercise Your Privacy Rights**.

4.1 Websites. To prevent the display of Publisher or Adknowledge advertising on a Website, for example, banner advertisements, do not visit the Website. To only prevent Adknowledge from tracking your behavior on a Website, turn off cookies from that Website and do not click on or interact with any advertisements. Adknowledge does not have a mechanism or process to respond to any “do not track” signals which a web browser may send or receive, other than as described in this section.

4.2 Email Databases. To unsubscribe from Adknowledge or Publisher email lists, click the link included in the footer of any message delivered by Adknowledge or a Publisher and follow the instructions provided. You may also unsubscribe from the Adknowledge network by visiting <http://docs.adknowledge.com/mus/index.php>. Please read the privacy policy for Adknowledge and its Publishers to understand how your Individual Information may be used after you unsubscribe.

4.3 Software Programs. To prevent software programs from displaying advertisements on your computer, uninstall the software program provided by an Adknowledge Publisher by following the instructions included in the privacy policy at the time of installation. Software programs should include an option to uninstall in the “Add/Remove Programs” section of the Windows® operating system, or by visiting the file director of the installed program and running an uninstaller executable.

4.4 Cookies. Check instructions about your web browser to learn how to prevent placement of, or how to remove, cookies placed on your computer by Adknowledge.

**More Information**

_Additional resources and contact information_.

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [http://www.netcoalition.com](http://www.netcoalition.com/) and [http://www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/). Adknowledge reserves the right to update this Policy at any time by republishing it to this Website with a new effective date. If you have questions about this Policy and your rights under this policy, or if you would like access to personal information we may have about you in our files, to correct, update, or to have us delete it, or would like to notify us of your choice to opt out of the sharing of any of your personal information, please contact us at privacy at adknowledge.com or write to us at:

Adknowledge, Inc.  
List Management Operations  
Attn: Privacy and Compliance Group  
4600 Madison, 10th Floor  
Kansas City, MO 64112  
USA
